uh Mr Cosby we're your lawyers I think
you know why we've called this meeting
of course I do because I Did the lose in
the so cold raping then the liqu and
the and the spe of the fluids you know
all over the place well well talking
like that uh in a deposition it's not a
good idea yeah we're going to need a a
really good defense a story you can
stick to story that I had hit TV show
when the dance and I
went bo bo bo bo and that's how we
opened the show it was a very successful
show um how about this Michael Jackson
Mike Tyson and you what do all three of
you have in common a come on now what
did you rap what did you lose then knock
them down and no no no no no no no
you're all successful black men yes okay
systematically taken down because White
America uh couldn't stomach it just like
OJ yes like o the Simpson not the juice
Mr Cosby it's a conspiracy a race-based
conspiracy correct
capito I mean I may regret this but that
does look delicious right I could use a
little afternoon pick me up I nope oh
look at that come on he's putting sugar
or whatever that is it's fine there you
go young man that was
it uh maybe uh these women were paid to
bring you down H maybe they entrapped
you yes you were just trying to Mentor
them you the real victim good that's
exactly right and then under theer suck
of the toes and the woo Woos and and the
look of the pudding
pop
smoothie I probably shouldn't but I did
skip lunch so maybe just have a little
M delicious is that banana well there's
some banana and some lons you know the
secret is in the news and that is a
great example of things you should
definitely not say during a deposition
agreed Council uh we need to be more
specific here let's think of some white
groups that would hate you the most hate
yes white liberals correct the mo no
that is exactly true white liberals hate
when you tell black teens to pull their
pants up is precisely what I've been
trying to tell you all this time and and
these belob are trying to take you down
because you tell teens to pull their
pants up that's right this could work I
like this no code oh it's a fun surprise
Don't Mind If I Do literally can't see
why I wouldn't to the Cosby and the
getting off and not in the sexual way
but in the legal
way Cosby you did it again
m